

EDUCATION

09/2016 - 05/2019 XX Secondary school | Szlak 5, 31-161 Kraków

10/2020 - now **Jagiellonian university** | ul. *Grodzka* 52, 33-332 Kraków

Studies: Comparative studies of civilizations

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- English C1
- Hindi B1
- Chinese A2 (plan to continue learnig)
- Driver's license cat. B.
- MS Office's package intermediate.
- Communication skill and open-mindedness.
- Customer service at the highest level.
- Commitment to the duties.
- Conscientiousness and precision.
- Very good organization skill.
- Willingness to constantly improve qualifications.
- Good manners.

Paulina Nowak

- 530901521
- paulina.novak13@gmail.com
- Mała Góra 15b/4, 30-864 Kraków

SUMMARY

I am a creative person, who is not afraid of new challenges and love to learn new skills. Owing to my one month staying in China I have started to be fascinate about journeys, discovering new places, cultures and people. What characterizes me is conscientiousness, hard-work and commitment to my duties, which I am trying to do on the highest level. I would like to improve in my job independently from position I have and gain new abilities to expanse my experience. I love to learn foreign languages and to program. Due to this, in July I have started Fullstack Developer 10-month course. In my job I find myself with people, with whom I can be myself.

EXPERIENCE

02/2019 - 05/2019

Castorama Polska Sp. z.o.o | Kraków Sales Advisor in the Horticulture Department

- Sale of goods.
- Adding commodity.
- Monitoring of deliveries and stock levels.
- Continuous broadening of knowledge about the products offered in the store.
- Maintaining a positive relations with clients.
- Customer service in the field of plant protection and garden care.

06/2019 - 01/2020

Columbus Coffee | Kraków

Barista

- · Preparing sandwiches and cakes.
- Brewing and serving coffee and other drinks.
- Opening and closing cafe, in which settlement of revenues.
- Cleaning the workplace and keeping the premises tidy.

CERTIFICATIONS & PROJECTS

- Google certificate "Basics of Internet Marketing".
- Cambridge certificate B2.
- Sololearn certificate "SQL course"

INTERESTS

I am interested in independent movies and Chinese and Japanese culture and history. I am very fond of going to art's exhibitions, learning foreign languages and to program. In my free time I like reading classics, fantasy books, and Asian writers works.

- Taking orders and billing guests.
- Taking care of equipment necessary for work.
- Cooperation with others baristas.
- Customer service, including foreigners.
- Recommending and selling products.
- Taking care of the good image of the comapny
- Maintaining positive relations with clients.
- Service cash register.

02/2020 - 08/2020

Coffeefield | Kraków Bartender/Shift Supervisor

- Preparing sandwiches and cakes.
- Brewing and serving coffee and other drinks.
- Opening and closing cafe, in which settlement of revenues.
- Cleaning the workplace and keeping the premises tidy.
- Taking orders and billing guests.
- Taking care of equipment necessary for work.
- Cooperation with others baristas.
- Customer service, including foreigners.
- Recommending and selling products.
- Taking care of the good image of the company
- Maintaining positive relations with clients.
- Service cash register.
- Preparation of alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages.
- Taking care of positive atmosphere at work and between employees.
- Coming up with interesting promotional campaigns.

09/2020 - 05/2021

McDonald's | Kraków

Restaurant worker

- Customer service in accordance with the standards of the premises.
- Keeping the kitchen and hall clean.
- Taking care of the highest level of preparing the food.
- · Accepting cash and non-cash payments.
- Taking orders and serving food.
- Supporting restaurants in achieving their goals.
- Taking care of the good image of the company.
- Service cash register.
- Brewing and serving coffee and other drinks from the menu.

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

